

JunWei Song

Security Engineer

Contact

Taiwan

sungboss2004@gmail.com

https://github.com/krnick

in /krnick

Education

National University of Kaohsiung, Master in Information Management, 2020

Public Speaking

HITBSecConf Armory, AMS, 2020. (URL)

PyCon TW/KR/MY 2019 (URL)

Personal Profile

JunWei is a Security Researcher from Taiwan. A paranoid Pythonista who focuses on cybersecurity, reverse engineering, and malware analysis. And as a CPython contributor, PyCon TW Review Board, presented at HITBSecConf, PyCon Taiwan, PyCon Korea, PyCon Malaysia. He's the co-founder of Quark-Engine and a security research group, TWBGC.

Work Experience

Telecom Technology Center, Taiwan, Security Engineer

October 2018 - Now (1.5 years) - working during master's degree

Develop an Android malicious behavior risk scoring system from zero to one, as Lead Developer, responsible for Quark core function design, program development, program testing, documentation writing. Communicate and coordinate with team members, and cooperate through Gitflow. Also actively promote this project to train new members.

Dowton Electronic Materials, Taiwan, Independent Contractor for network infrastructure

March 2017 - June 2017 (3 months) - working during college

Galaxy Software Services Corporation, Taiwan, Web Development Intern

July 2016 - August 2016 (2 months) - working during college

Security Research



<u>CVE-2019-9674</u>: zip bomb in Python zipfile module.

Technical Blog



CPython-internals

Analysis of CPython interpreter implementation principles and CPython source code analysis.

Books Reviewer



- 職業駭客的修練:機械碼與底層的把玩藝術
- 職業駭客的告白II部曲:Python和Ruby啟 發式程式語言的秘密
- 職業駭客的告白III部曲:C語言、組合語言 與逆向工程的秘密
- 駭客的修練:使用IDA Pro進行底層分析

P y C o n C o m m u n i t y



- Member of PyCon Taiwan Program Team since 2020
- Member of PyCon Review Board since 2020

Authored Open-Source Projects

Quark-Engine An Obfuscation-Neglect Android Malware Scoring System.

<u>sunzip</u> a Python package, providing secure unzip against zip bomb.

<u>gwalstat-bot</u> A bot for checking github pull requests.

Open source contributions

<u>CPython</u>



- 1. Find the Zip Bomb vulnerability and successfully apply for a CVE number in Python zipfile module.
- 2. Writing zipfile module decompression pitfalls in Python official documentation.
- 3. Typo error and helped to correct in zipfile module.
- 4. Typo error and helped to correct in email.generator module.

Androguard



- 1. Provide an example to allows users to query the decompilation instruction set corresponding to a specific function.
- 2. Solve the problem of dependency packages and remind users in official documentation.